[{"answer": "When we were listening -- we're in court this morning and we were listening to the state's case, you know, we were all thinking, oh, you know, that's it.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Where are we left here, do you think?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Reeva was -- she was exceptional.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "She has such this multi-facetted kind of career that she was building for herself, but what kind of woman was she?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "That's very hard.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "How did you hear that she had died?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "It was terrible.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "How would you sum up the atmosphere given the appalling circumstances of her death?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Well, I saw it in the -- in the news first, and that was about only two months ago.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "When did Reeva tell you that she was dating Oscar Pistorius?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "I think the family are devastated.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "How would you describe the family reaction to him?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "No, Piers, you know, we were all in shock that Reeva died the way she did.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Any suggestion that it was a volatile relationship or anything about all that?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "You know something, Piers, I -- that is what in my heart I hope and wish is the truth because I would not like to think that my cousin suffered.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Do you or do the family think that is a possibility?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "For her sense of humor, for her kindness, her magical presence.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "And finally, Kim, how would you like Reeva to be remembered?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, obviously I don't know.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Where are you with this?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Well, let me start with the affidavit, and this is like a little inside dirty secret in the legal profession.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "What evidentially have you seen which can be backed up by any apparent fact which actually says he did murder her?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, I mean let me come back to Alan.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Piers, really?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "He shot first and asked questions later is his explanation.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Vinnie, very quickly, finally, just tell me the one thing that you have heard which you believe points to his guilt as a cold- blooded murder?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Piers, I was at work when I -- I had I heard the -- the, you know -- the ongoing coverage all day long, but I was at work when I found out about Adam Lanza and, sadly, my friend, Nancy, who I knew then, who was no longer with us.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Where were you when you hear the news about what Adam Lanza did at Sandy Hook School?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I just -- you know, I knew she loved her son.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Was that your impression?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "She was a wonderful friend.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "What kind of woman was Nancy Lanza?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I don't know that it was that she felt she needed them.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Why would she feel the need for all that?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Well, as far as Nancy goes, she was -- you know, she was trained in how to use a gun and in proper gun safety.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "And what does that tell you, I guess, about the problems with dealing with mental health perhaps in relation to gun violence?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, I was rather shocked that he said such a thing because basically I've taught about 7,000 women how to shoot.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "What was your reaction to what Vice President Biden had to say?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Well, I agree with him that I think an AR-15 is not something that the normal, average citizen should have.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What would your response be to that?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Well, as you know, I am a gun owner, and I do own a shotgun.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "When you heard Joe Biden say what he said, what did you think of it?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "This goes into your bra.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "This one goes in your bra?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "UIGLEY: No.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Are you content that more and more women buy weapons through this kind of direct marketing that they're like the next Chanel handbag?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I don't agree that's the answer either, Piers.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "What do you say to people that believe that is the only solution?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "It's -- it's a mixed sort of bag of feelings because, you know, the three of us, we're the best of friends.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Patrick, how has it been dealing with his loss?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Well, it's that wonderful bittersweet.", "docId": "130220pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "How do you feel when you hear him talking?", "qSentId": 527}]